today and tomorrow which is the 11th in
the US.
Uh kind of not commemorating I we we are
looking back. It was on the 11th of 2019
of April that Julian Assange was
snatched and grabbed by the Metropolitan
Police in London and made a political
prisoner at Gilmore Prison. So why I am
here today is that comrade Misty said to
me like a month ago we're going to do
something in New in in DC. I said write
me down. Sure. I'll be there. And then
like 3 weeks ago said we're doing April
11th. And I didn't realize at the time
that well that's the day that Julian was
snatched and graphed and put into this
what really is a medieval medieval
media media a medieval fortress in
London. It's like uh the tower of London
is a luxury suite compared to where he
is right now. So, and I said not only
that, but that's the anniversary of this
show. I started with the help of
Margaret Kler and others and Julian
Assange on April 11th, 2017,
which was the uh program Assange
Countdown to Freedom, which was on WBAI
at that time. It was that day with
Julian and John Pillager. We kicked off
that show. So, that was five years ago.
Two years ago, two years later, Julian
was snatched and grabbed by Metropolitan
Police and mummified basically in this
uh horrible prison uh that you would
it's okay for if you were Hannibal
Lecter, but not for one of the great
minds of our time, one of the great uh
individuals, one of the great humans of
our time, one of the great talented
individuals ever is there right now. and
we'll all talk about that later on, the
different reasons why he is there. We
have an incredible cast. I'm going to
basically do the Ed Sullivan routine
tonight. I'm going to be introducing
performers and Katie Halper is going to
help me with that. Uh because uh this is
not about, as I said earlier, about
other issues. There's a lot of issues
right now. There's a war in Yemen. Uh
and there's a war in Venezuela and and
they're trying to overthrow the
government of Cuba. US is committing
crimes around the world. There's a war
that's been going on for eight years in
Ukraine. I don't want to get into those
subjects tonight. I want to get into
Julian Assange because he is dying in
that [__] prison. And we have to
focus on that tonight. And I hope
everyone will indulge that thought
tonight and focus on Julian Assange
because there's a war going on right
here. And it's a war on the very
democracy. what's left of it in this
country. It's a war on the first
amendment. It's a war on free speech and
it's being lodged by our government
through Julian Assange. There is a war
we are if he goes whatever we have left
of this democracy is gone as John Piller
has said. So we are here to fight back
against the war on the first amendment
and the strongest pillar of democracy in
this country which is the first
amendment and the entire bill of rights
right now is happening and we have to
fight back and that's why I am here
tonight. This is the fourth event.
Humorous. It's standups. I say humorous.
Satis for Assange is what I should say.
And we have a great cast. We have a
great uh group of comedians and speakers
tonight. And uh you know,
I get very upset thinking about it that
here we are tonight. We're all having a
good time. And that guy Julian Sons
23 hours a day
23 hours a day this great mind cutting
off the fingers of Beethoven Brahms
Dubai is what they've done
and tomorrow I'm here because comrade
Misty said come down on the 11th and I
said okay I'll exploit it and do this on
the 10th and say it's the 11th
And we'll do tomorrow in front of the uh
I What do you think? I have good vision.
All right. I'm Mr. Magcoo. I can barely
see uh that you gave that to me. But
tomorrow
in front of um in front of uh early the
British consulate, which is the US
consulate basically because the US cons
US controls the British consulate. There
will be a demonstration at 10:00 in the
morning. Am I right, Combert Misty?
Yes, you're right.
And where is that located?
Um, it's at the British Embassy. It's uh
right by the the It's on uh let's see 31
Mass
3100 Massachusetts Avenue 10:00 in the
morning. I will be there. And then
there's one at 2:00 in front of
We're hitting both countries. DOJ
the DOJ.
Yeah, the DOJ two.
I hope Venita Gupta comes out and says
hello to us. All right, that's 2
o'clock. That's 10 o'clock. And that so
this is important that you show up
tonight, but it's more important that
you show up tomorrow. So everybody
that's here tonight, it's important
right now that we go on the streets
cuz there is no chance that Julian is
going to be freed unless the asses of
the masses are on the street. It It's on
us. And tomorrow is the beginning of
that. I mean, we've done this before.
Chuck and uh my good friend Bernardet, I
know her name. What do you think?
I'm Rain Man, right?
So, Chuck Confered that uh we we were
here like way back in August. It was 175
degrees outside and we did something
with two other people that came by
selling Italianis and that
was
Yes. And Media was there. She came and
did an interview and then she melted and
went away. But she's speaking tonight.
So, um,
uh, that being said, um, and then two
o'clock in front of the DOJ, it's really
important that we get out there because
this is a fight. This we are we are the
Abraham Lincoln Brigade fighting against
evil right now. And we have to get out
there and fight and support because this
republic is dying right now. If they are
able to silence during Assange for good,
we need to fight for it. It's the fight.
I know it's a lost cause to some people.
Those are the only ones worth fighting
for. And uh tonight we're going to talk
hear from a lot of great speakers. Um
I'm going to get someone that knows
who's been through this to kick it off.
He's done. Every event I've done in this
city, this man always says, "I'm there."
He spent two years in prison. He exposed
CIA torture
and he has devoted his life
on behalf of the good fight. And you all
know who he is. It's John Kyaku. Give
him a big round of applause.
Hi everybody.
Good job.
Usually I try to come with a joke. I'm
not funny, but I try.
Neither
am I tonight.
I I can't I can't tonight. It's uh you
we've gotten to crunch time. So, I'll
I'll view my role tonight as bringing
the crowd down
so that our sadderist friends can uh
bring it back up again. You know, I've
been thinking about this a lot and uh I
I mentioned the last time I was here
that that Julian's um family has accused
me in a very friendly way of being
overly optimistic. And uh I I've come to
realize that that they're right. I have
been overly optimistic in the process. I
just have believed that Julian's case
was so crystal clear and our concerns
for his human rights and his civil
rights and civil liberties has been so
clear that he couldn't lose.
And even as he began losing in the
British uh uh judicial system, I
convinced myself that cooler heads would
prevail. I realized that I was wrong.
And so I've come to the conclusion that
from now on it's up to us,
right? We're the ones that have to take
this to the streets and to the courts.
Julian, in the event that he is
extradited, and it's coming up to crunch
time. Today's the 10th. The uh
Westminster court is supposed to send
his extradition to Pretty Patel on the
20th. And then I'm assuming now that
she's going to order his extradition.
And so, God forbid he'll he'll he could
be here by the end of the month.
And so when he comes, I'm going to say
when, he'll come to the Eastern District
of Virginia, the espionage court.
Forgive me if this is repetitive,
but I've had personal experience in the
Eastern District of Virginia. He cannot
and will not get a fair trial.
It's not possible. His jury will be made
up of people who work for or who have
friends and relatives working for the
CIA, which is in the Eastern District of
Virginia, the Pentagon, which is in the
Eastern District of Virginia, the
Department of Homeland Security, the
FBI, and any one of dozens of
intelligence community contractors. The
deck is stacked.
In my own experience,
when I was facing trial after I blew the
whistle on the CIA's torture program, my
best friend's wife had an uncle, if you
can keep it all straight, who was OJ
Simpson's jury consultant.
Yeah. I thought, "Oh, I've got it made
now."
He came up to Washington. We got him a
security clearance. He went through
15,000 pages of classified discovery.
And he said to me, "If we were in any
other district in America, I would say,
let's go for it. We're going to win this
thing." But the Eastern District of
Virginia, he said, "Buddy, you don't
stand a chance. Take the deal." And so I
took the deal. Julian's not being
offered a deal. He's facing more than
what, a century, century and a half in
prison, something like
175 years.
How much was 175 years?
175 years in prison. 50 when he gets
out.
Yeah, he'll be 250 years old when he
gets out. So, uh there there's no
there's no deal on the table. That's why
I say it's up to us in the event that he
comes. We have to be at that court every
single day. We have to be in the
courtroom. We have to be outside the
courthouse because that's where the
media is going to be. and they have to
understand that he has a core of support
that's willing to throw down for him.
We have to be there to convince the
likes of the Washington Post and the New
York Times and the Wall Street Journal
that if Julian goes down for this,
they're going down next
because this is a very slippery slope.
You know, I participated in a Zoom
meeting not too long ago that included
two former reporters for Night Ribbon,
and neither one of them mentioned Julian
through the entire presentation. And
then finally in the Q&A at the very end
of it, somebody said, "Well, wait a
minute. What about Julian Assange? We've
been talking for an hour and a half and
nobody's mentioned Julian Assange." And
one of these Nightrider uh reporters
said, "Oh, I don't view him as a as a
journalist. I view him as an activist."
Well, you know what? Even if you don't
view him as a journalist, he's certainly
a publisher.
And if a guy who's not even an American
citizen
can go to prison for 175 years for
releasing information that the public
owns, by the way, the American public
own that information. Yeah,
he pays that price and is not an
American citizen, is not compelled by
law to protect the information in the
first place, that every national
security journalist in America is next.
Every last one.
So, let's all be there. Let's be there
when they bring him in. We'll be there
for every preliminary hearing. We'll be
there for the trial. will be there to
give interviews out front to every
reporter who's going to be there. And
you know that there are going to be
reporters from all over the world. And
people have to understand that he's not
alone.
That he has all of us. And there are a
lot of us.
So let's keep up the fight. Now the
stakes are high. Now is when the fight
begins. Thank you very much.
What? You're an American hero.
Thank you. You
really are. You sacrifice a lot
and you never scare yourself. You are
out there. You do all of the different
podcasts, radio shows. You've been here
every single time and I really salute
you for that. I think this audience will
too. John Keryak. Thank you.
I want to give a shout out to the people
uh that have been uh out there for Julia
watching this show tonight. I know that.
And first of all, John Pilter. Give him
a big round of applause. John,
Neils Meler, what about Nils Melzer?
Craig Murray, the great Craig Murray,
and uh individual that uh saved my life
by getting me this little dog
and that is Roger Waters. Roger Waters.
It was the Paul Rosen of our time. Paul
Rosen of our time is Roger Waters.
It is
today.
Wow. What a coincidence. a lot of
coincidences today, but um I want to
thank all of those people. I want to
thank you all for coming in. Um and
we're going to keep this show rolling
and we're going to be doing things. I
talked to Katie. What do I We're We're
kind of like improvising our way through
this. All right. So, uh we're going to
be going to comedian to musician to a
speaker. So, uh, please, uh, be, uh,
very, uh, thoughtful of, uh, the
performers. And we're going to go to
comedy right now, and then we're going
to go to music. And, uh, this, uh, John
F. O'Donnell,
who's one of those,
they better know me.
Well, he's one of those that was a
correspondent for redacted tonight,
which was silenced by US Justice
Department. Uh, they have silenced RT.
Why? Why? I I do RT. Why not? I mean,
I've been on MSNBC. I know it's like
government control. I mean, you think
that Mary Melbour doesn't get like like
something on the side, you know, from
those guys. All right. So there's no
pure news broadcast in this country.
It's like you watch MSNBC and CNN, you
get five. It's all panel discussions and
and they're it's like you it's so
skewed. It's like remember the Mlathan
group?
Sure.
All right. It's like the Mlathan group
where you got five points of view. The
right, the far right, the extreme right,
the fascist right, and the third right.
That's what you got in those groups. And
that is what's happening today on these
shows. There's no there's no it's like
Jim Steoto, he's going to survive. If
Julian Sans goes to prison, he and Jim
Acasta and their, you know, their tubs
of grill cream will survive for a long
period of time. The same way when they
broke out of the uh display window at
Saks Fifth Avenue where they were like
this.
One guy gets it, man. Thank you, John.
He's the only guy he still uses
girlfriend. All right.
All right. So, uh, those people. What is
he doing? Is he praying over here?
It's all right. You're dressed in black.
I figured, you know,
one of those guys from India that does
that.
Fisher.
All right. Dressed like that. All right.
Steve Brown. Steve Brown, by the way.
Hey, Steve. Uh Steve Brown, if you don't
know who he is, is on the board at
Cobert Action Magazine. And Lou,
where's Lou Wolf? Over here, who I met
in 1986
is a co-founder with Ellen Ray and Bill
Sha. And I remember I was at the event
in I think it was somewhere in Boston,
right?
Was in Cambridge. We did some kind of
event for corporate Action magazine. And
uh that's when I first met. That's like
almost 40 years ago. And it was about
the war in Nicaragua in the counter
insurgency
in El Salvador. And I went there and I
did my Reagan impression. Yes, I
remember that you was doing my Reagan
back then and thees have done it again.
Honduras and I have a photograph that
bears me out.
Well, it's not exactly a photograph.
It's a shadow grab. As you can see, the
guy with the duck head is all right.
That was what I did back in at that
event.
Please give this guy some speed. Line of
blow or anything, man. They don't have
anybody got some clean blow here.
I tried cocaine one day for 20 years and
I said,
"It's not work out, man. I got to get
away from it.
So, that's it, man. All right. So, uh,
we're going to move to comedy right now.
So, John F. I No, I've already
introduced you John F. We've been pacing
back and forth. I want you to keep it
down to 1 minute and 30 seconds. I'm
kidding. We've already discussed this.
He's actually very funny and one of the
originals at the great show redacted
tonight, which has been redacted by the
US government. Would you please welcome
John F. Oanl.
[Applause]
Cool. And how about John, guys? John,
give John.
Is this mic working? Okay.
Awesome. I'm John. Um, uh, yeah, it's
good to be back in DC. I haven't I
haven't been back in DC for a few years,
so it's good to be back here. Uh, give
yourselves a round of applause for
coming out. Come on, give yourselves a
round of applause. We're showing
solidarity, enjoying time.
This uh, I remember when I was in DC
doing shows all the time for like uh, I
guess I would call them sort of
political normies, you know, like DC
normies. I would always ask them
something about Edward Snowden, but I
think it also applies to Julian Assange.
I would say this. I would ask him a
question. And I would go I would go
round of applause if you think Edward
Snowden is a hero. And I get this little
trickle of like
of like nervous applause. And then I
would say round of applause if you think
he's a traitor. And again it'd be this
little trickle of like
and then I'd say round of applause if
you didn't applaud because you're
maneuvering for political position.
You're not sure who's around. You don't
want to reveal how you feel about the
situation. Everyone be like, "Yeah,
that's me. That's me. I'm in the third
category. My moral compass is broken. My
moral compass is broken. I want to be a
congressional staffer. I want to be a
congressional staffer. I want to work
for Mitch McConnell. Yeah. I want to
work for a turtleface man with a jolly
gullet. Yeah. I want to work for a
turtleface man with a jolly gullet.
Yeah. And if I do a good job, maybe
he'll pee on me or whatever.
[Laughter]
I just wanted to see what happened if I
got dirty up top. You know what I mean?
Ever following a hero CIA whistleblower
turn my Mitch McConnell joke into a
peeing joke right up top in solidarity
with Julian? This is the comedy portion
of the show, you guys. This is the
comedy portion of the show. Let's have
some fun, right?
Wouldn't Julian want us to have some
[__] fun right now, huh?
That's how I feel about it. So, let me
tell you who I am. Let me get
vulnerable. Let me get honest. I'm John.
I'm a sober vegan conspiracy theorist
with bipolar disorder
who lives with his mom in suburban New
Jersey. I do not sound cool on paper.
But let me explain myself. I'm sober
because I have bipolar disorder. So I
have to be according to my doctors
plural. I'm vegan also because I have
bipolar disorder because it's important
to have a a low inflammation diet. It's
really good for the brain and being
vegan is a good way to do it. So, I'm
vegan for that reason. I'm also vegan
for ethical reasons concerning the
environment and animal rights is what I
tell aging hippie boomers so they'll
give me hand jobs.
What does it work?
What?
I'm a conspiracy theorist because I'm
paying attention.
I have bipolar disorder because of
ill-advised LSD experimentation in high
school. I think
probably
I live with my mom in suburban New
Jersey because all of my money is tied
up in cryptocurrency.
This is who I am. Which begs the
question, do you guys know my mom?
Do you guys know Pam? Do you guys know
Pammy? Do you guys know my mom? Do you
guys know Pamela? She's pretty cool. I
love her a lot. But that being said, her
primary email address is an optline.net
email address. She uses the email
address that's given out as the cable
provider as her main email address.
Gross. I can barely love her anymore.
But that being said, she needs to hold
on to that email because she created a
Gmail email address. And for real, the
Gmail email address she created is lest
we forget 911gmail.com.
[Music]
Yeah, I like it.
For real.
I like it.
And I was like, "Mom, why did you create
the email addresses we forget 911?" I
show up. She was like, "While I was
watching television, there was a
commercial on TV for September 11th
commemorative coins, and I figured no
one would have that email address."
Yeah. No [__] No one has any.
Could you imagine somebody did like,
"Oh, let's try less wee forget
911_1"@gmail.com.
If you have the email address less we
forget 911@gmail.com. You can't send
like a casual email.
You can't be like, "Hey, Pammy here, aka
lessforget 911@gmail.com.
Just want to remind everybody about the
bake sale.
I'll be doing my famous snicker doodle
cookies. Carol, you're going to do red
velvet cupcakes. Oh, and Terry, you're
going to do brownies. But don't forget,
a lot of kids have nut allergies, so
keep the ones with the nuts away from
the ones without the nuts. Never forget
about the nut allergies. Never forget.
Never forget. Never forget about the nut
allergies. If you have the email address
less, we forget 911@gmail.com.
The only person you can email is like
Dick Cheney
because we all know he orchestrated the
entire thing and that's why I've called
you all here tonight. Please immediately
after the show, go to
www.tabardin.com/jet
fuel cannot melt steel beans
and read everything on that web page.
And if you still have any questions
afterwards, feel free to email my mom.
All right.
Yeah, man.
Thank you for that.
You got it, my man. So, uh, yeah. So,
maybe like IRL, I'm not doing great, but
I am
I'm rushing it on the internet. I am the
most popular John by far on the
internet. Thank you. First page, second
page, third page, fourth page, all me,
all this guy. That being said,
interestingly, the ninth entry on the
first page is not about me. It's a
different John F. O'Donnell. Who is it,
you ask? Brigadier General John F.
O'Donnell.
He got the number nine spot.
Sure, why not? All he's done is been a
command pilot in the United States
[__] Air Force, who's logged more
than 200 hours in the air and partaken
in more than 250 combat missions while
flying either his F4 Phantom or his F104
Starf Fighter son. And his military
decorations include what? I don't know.
The Legion of Merit, the Distinguished
Flying Cross, the Bronze Star Medal, the
Air Medal, and the Air Force Commenation
Medal. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But he ain't got his own website, son.
Suck your freaking dear, General John F.
O'Donnell. You ain't on Twitter. You
ain't on Instagram. You ain't got no
podcast. Probably because you were born
in 1930 and died in 2005.
But whatever. Get your [__] together.
Your internet's presence is pathetic,
man.
And here's my favorite part, you guys.
There's no way in a million years, man,
in 1969, man, when Brigadier General
Jonathan was flying over northern
Vietnam, man, and dropping God knows how
many tons of napom and cluster bombs in
the Vietnamese people that he ever could
have imagined in his wildest dreams.
that part of the freedom he was fighting
for was in fact the freedom for me
comedian John O'Donnell to include him,
Brigadier General John O'Donnell in my
adorable little comedy routine.
God bless you Brigadier General John F
O'Donnell. You are a patriot sir. You
are a patriot sir andor a war criminal
or a war criminal sir
depending on who you talk to.
Vietnam, man. Be it [__] now, man.
Everybody 1 2 3. Be it [__] now, man.
1 2 3. Be it [__]
man.
Isn't that like bizarrely cathartic?
Yeah. I um Let's talk about the elephant
in the room. Let's talk about what you
guys want to talk about. Say it with me.
You guys want to talk about the US back
right-wing coup that happened in Bolivia
a couple years that nobody knows about.
Boom. day all day. I know when a group
of Assange reporters want to talk about
the US back right-wing coup that
happened in Bolivia a couple years ago
that nobody knows about, but probably
people in this room do know about it.
Uh I don't bring it up to be political.
I only bring it up because this coup
apparently was over lithium because it's
believed that Bolivia has the world's
largest reserves of lithium and it's
thought that lithium is going to become
an even more valuable resource than
fossil fuels because of how it's used to
power all sorts of technology,
electronics and you know batteries and
computers and stuff like that, right?
So, here's the thing. Generally
speaking, I'm against resource-based
regime change wars, but
but I have bipolar disorder.
I'm on lithium.
I take lithium every day. I need me that
lithium. Otherwise, every two years or
so, I think I'm Jesus Christ,
which is not a sustainable way to
maintain a comedy career.
Or, as it turns out, a viable credit
score.
Why? Cuz Messiah don't give a [__] about
paying his bills on time. He got [__] to
do. He don't care if his [__] goes into
default. He be Messiah. So, in this one
particular instance, I got to say, [__]
the indigenous people of Bolivia
and their inherent right to benefit off
their own natural resources. [__] them.
I can't have the democratically elected
socialist leader of Bolivia
nationalizing all the lithium, keeping
it out of the grabby hands of the US
imperialist piggy pigs.
Give me that lithium. Otherwise, I don't
know. I'm going to have to be cracking
open iPhones and swallowing the
batteries.
Oh, look at John. What's he doing? He's
running down the road trying to catch up
with a Tesla so he can wrap his lips
around the tail pipe and suck out the
precious metals. A
come to think of it, Teslas are electric
cars. They don't even have uh tail
pipes. Looks like John going to have to
find himself the electric the Energizer
Bunny. Remember the Energizer Bunny? And
then I'm just going to have to gently
plug my penis inside the Energizer
Bunny's electrical socket butthole and
get charged up. Charge me up, Bunny.
Charge me up, Bunny. Oh, this part of
the joke's real weird.
So it only works like 50% of the time,
you know, this not being one of those
times and I'm just stuck up here just
like [__] an imaginary bunny from
behind. You know what I mean? But
sometimes that's what comedy is.
Elon Musk,
you know what? [__] you Elon Musk for
that [__] Elon Musk is like a
concistador of the global south for
their minerals and resources. We think
he's like the cool richest guy in the
world. And thank you for saying that
because I had no way to get out of my
joke, but that worked. Good laugh line
and applause line. So, thank you on
that. Uh, and I'm Jonathan. Thank you.
[Applause]
That was And so he's missing from
Redacted tonight and so is Jaffre
and so is Lee Camp. Those other two will
be on a little later. And uh and so is
my good friend, one of the greatest
journalists of our time, and that is
Ashen Ratanzi. You know who he is.
Give him a nice big round of applause
for all the great points we have.
Amazing.
[Applause]
They don't classify MSNBC or CNN or Fox
as US governmentont controlled news
agencies, but they are seriously right.
Whether indirectly or directly, I mean,
Operation Mocky Bird is still alive and
well. and and somebody said, "Well, I
think John, that's that all of these
correspondents are going to lose their
job." I can tell you that those at Wolf
Blitzer will not lose his job. He will
continue to be there. Or Kendallian or
any of those other fake journalists,
they will not lose their jobs. Okay?
Neither will Chuck Todd, neither will uh
Jake Tapper. They will continue because
they go along to get along and that's
what it's all about. All right, Julian
Assange. These guys all together
are not a patch on his ass as a
journalist.
Am I right? Yeah,
I was watching
I was watching two nights ago the movie
Spartacus
and the one moment that really struck me
Spartacus going against what was you
know back then the US government which
was the Roman Empire against Marcus
Cassus
and uh they lost and then when they
tried to find out who the one guy was
who the one guy was who inspired all of
these people Spartacus
They rounded up all of the prisoners and
they said, "Who is Spartacus?"
And then one after another said, "I am
Spartacus." I am Spartacus. So today,
who is the one guy, Julian Assange? I
want to ask everybody beginning with
you, Chuck, who is the leader, who is
Julian Assange? I want you to start it
and I want everyone to say that we are
Julian Assange. So, who is Julian
Assange that we're going after, Chuck?
I am Julian Assange.
Who is Julian Assange?
Everybody,
thank you.
I didn't hear from you.
Come on, Steve.
Steve, you're not working with CNN, are
you?
[Music]
Steve Jones.
Good. Yeah.
All right. So, um, right now, uh, we're
going to bring up we're going to some
wonderful music tonight. Uh, Eleanor
Goldfield was here at our last event and
knocked the place out. She really did.
Who was here for that night? She's a
award-winning documentarian.
She is a fantastic singer and she is
here tonight. Would you please welcome
Elner Goldfield? Give her a big round of
applause.
[Applause]
Give me one second.
Hold on.
Hold, please.
I know. Yeah. I just feel like I got to
pull the time somehow. Um, so for all
those who were here last time, y'all are
about to hear the same three songs cuz I
got a fourmonth old and a [__] ton of
boxes, [__] ton of moving boxes at home.
So, my ass has not picked up this guitar
since the last time I was here. So, it's
it's going to be a little rusty.
Uh, but we're going to get through it
together.
Uh, and last time
I asked y'all to sing along.
And this time I feel like I'm going to
need a little bit more. So, let's all
sing along in solidarity. I'm going to
call on you again the last song, but not
this song cuz it's mine. Again, I'm not
going to be a dick and ask you to sing
along.
Unless you can, in which case just make
my
So, shameless self-promotion. Oh, duh.
Um,
shameless self-promotion. Uh, this song
is off of my new EP,
which you can find on my website, part
ofkillingpathy.com.
Or if you sign up for Leeamp's Patreon
at leamp or no, at patreon.com/leamp
for $25 or more, you'll get a vinyl of
this EP.
You know, because Lee Camp had to start
a Patreon because the US government Shut
down.
[Music]
I stand
a pile of bricks on my feet.
Build me a road. I was searching for
something to see.
But who's got the time to split the
summer night?
[Music]
Cuz the hours of days and days we've
come to this place.
Oh, the world's on fire and I'm going to
stay where it burns.
I built this p and I'm going to stay
where it burns.
[Music]
I would say
I'm right here where it burns.
[Music]
[Applause]
You remember the time we stood through
the
Well, now it's past.
Fast forward behind you.
Home was a fire. I can feel this burn.
[Music]
What do you live for? Time to kill
forever.
Oh, the world's on fire. But I'm going
to stand where it burns.
We built this fire. I'm going to s
[Music]
I'm still
All right.
Who here hates fascists?
Really? I don't know who.
like, "Oh, I kind of hate fascists." You
know, depends. All right. Well, that's
awkward, but okay. Well, then this song
may or may not be for you.
I'll tell all you fascist
be
[Music]
cuz the people around this world are
getting
[Music]
bound to lose
all you fascists. You know you're bound
to lose.
Hey all you fascists.
Hey all you fascists. You're bound to
lose. You're bound to lose.
[Music]
Feel free to sing along.
Well tell all you fascist. You may be
surprised as people around this world
are getting
you bound to lose.
Hey fascists, you know you're bound to
lose.
[Music]
Hey you fascists.
Hey you fascist.
Hey, are you fascinated?
[Music]
Fascist, you're bound to lose.
Hey, fascist, you know you're bound to
lose.
H you fascist.
Hey you fascist. Hey you fascist.
Sorry
[Music]
you fascist.
Hey
Hey, are you
Thank you.
[Music]
Steve Jones.
Steve Jones. Steve Jones has been doing
this at every one of these events. You
know who's not here tonight? You know,
I've been doing this show. I saw his
countdown of freedom for 5 years. It
also began April 11th. As I said
earlier, I'm getting old. I'm a triple
AAA kid. My family, my lineage. Triple
A. It's
alcoholism.
It's arthritis and Alzheimer's. So, if I
repeat myself,
hi, I'm Randy. I'm an alcoholic.
It's a retail meeting. Yes.
You're good, man. You're good.
All right. Would you please see if this
guy is still breathing next to you?
Steve Brown, I want to tell you
something. Rescued Assange's Countdown
to Freedom in 2020 cuz I am the worst
fundraiser in the world. I cannot I
would never be hired by the Salvation
Army because I cannot raise [__]
money. I just can't say I can't do it.
But uh when we were going under, Steve
Brown came through and we got some great
volunteers. Uh and one of them who
couldn't make it tonight is my engineer
and uh editor, Kelly Lane. She got very
sick. She was coming up today and uh
and she couldn't make it. So a shout out
to you, Kelly Lane, for all the hard
work that you've done to keep this
going. Um, that being said, again,
tomorrow at 10:00 a.m. in the morning,
it's important. Tell your friends to
show up at the uh US uh lackey
government uh council of the UK
government, you know, uh Major Strasser
has told them that uh you they got to
continue the fight to squaltch the first
amendment, uh the UK government. So they
are totally
totally on board with uh whatever they
say here in the US to try to keep Julie
Assange from what are they afraid of?
One guy, one guy here, one individual.
They've spent, you go to the city, you
know, you show up at Union Station and
you see hundreds of people sleeping on
on the sidewalk or on a bench there.
There's tens of thousands of people
homeless in this city, 75,000 in New
York City. They don't have money for
that,
but they have hundreds of millions of
dollars to try to kill Julian Assange.
All right, that's where if they would
stop the prosecution, take that money
and put it into the homeless problem in
this country, we could solve it. But
that's more important to them that they
not allow Julie Assange
to speak.
Unbelievable.
Really, that's what this is all about.
And I want to thank everybody here
tonight for being here. And I want to
thank everybody for speaking out. Uh I'm
going to bring up right now someone who
had the most incredible show uh about
two months ago right after uh I forgot
the there's so many epics in the Julian
Assange um what you call a the Kafka s
show trial. Uh, and uh,
Katie Halpert did a great show along
with uh, Maryanne Williamson and Briana
uh, Joey Gray. They put this great show
together and I'm just very honored to be
part of it on uh, that one particular
day and she's been on it and we're doing
this right now on Katie. You know, I was
going to put on my YouTube account and I
said, "Oh, I only have a thousand, you
know, subscribers." She's got like
67,000. I said, "As many people, of
course, I might pick up some new
subscribers, but that's not it's not
about me. It's about getting the [__]
message out there." And Katie had the
vehicle to do it. And uh she's been
really on top of this issue. you know
her uh uh from Useful Idiots with Matt
Taibbei, sometimes with Aaron Mate and
sometimes with I don't know if you
rotate the uh your your your
uh co-host, but u she's here today and
she's going to come up here and talk
about the situation and she's going to
bring up uh my favorite presidential
candidate of all time afterwards. Uh
would you please welcome uh the
wonderful dog loving Ken Hill.
[Music]
[Applause]
Hi everyone.
I I feel kind of awkward stepping on
Julian As.
I'm going to do it right now. How about
his name?
Sure.
It's a metaphor. Hi everyone. How's
everyone doing?
Hello.
It's great to be here in DC. I feel like
I have a special place in my heart for
Washington DC. So, just to get where I'm
really from out of the way, I'm from New
York City.
Um, I'm the product of a mixed marriage.
U, my mom is Bronxian, my dad is
Queensian,
and they were both part of the great
Jewish migration from the outer burrows
into Manhattan's Upper West Side.
I can't tell if they're non New Yorkers
or anti-semmites in the crowd.
All right. Uh, yeah, they were searching
for a better life as close to zars as
possible.
Uh, but I did, uh, grow up hearing a lot
of stories about Washington DC because
my parents, well, my mom would tell me
stories about the anti-war movement,
about the civil rights movement. Like
instead of lullabibies, they would tell
me those stories, but effectively put me
to sleep, so they worked well. Um, but I
didn't really understand them. So my mom
used to tell me about how she went to
the march on Washington and I thought
she visited a friend who was a king
named Martin Luther and that he had a
dream that he told her about the next
day. Like that's really I mean despite
how funny that punchline is, that's
actually true. I'm not making a joke.
That's actually true. That's really what
I thought. Um but my mom did not have a
sleepover with Martin Luther King. Many
people did, but
well, although lots of women did not say
anything, but
yeah, lots of women did. It's It's okay.
It's not too soon there's been a foyer
about it.
But my mom did come close to dating
another civil rights hero. Um, he
doesn't have quite as much cred as MLK,
but my mom did briefly date Marin Barry.
Yeah. who would you know later become
the mayor of Washington DC before being
forced to step down miss a crack cocaine
prostitution scandal like you haven't
been there
the great part of that story though is
that he got his job back again which is
the American dream
but uh they met they met during the
civil rights movement uh I always say
that of all the snick meetings and all
the history in the world she had to walk
into his
That's the grown one. It's literally the
most wholesome joke ever. He went to a
meeting for the student body
coordinating committee. You guys are
like, "Wow, really, Katie?" Sorry, John.
John, I need you here to make some jokes
about like fornicating with a Tesla
battery.
All right, let's see. Uh, anyway, if
your mom dates someone like Mary, it's
not like that useful. So if your mom
dates someone like Martin Luther King
then whenever your dad mad at your dad
you could be like you're not my father.
Martin Luther King is my father but it
doesn't work Mary as I learned the hard
way. Um but yeah so my parents we are
from the upper west side as I mentioned
before to uporious uh laughter um that
you may not remember because that's how
loud it was. You have now a kind of PTSD
from it and it's knocked your memory out
but uh it's true my parents we're we're
Jewish but like we're not religious
Jews. So, I grew up not celebrating any
Jewish holidays except for Passover,
which I thought was the black holiday
like Quanza, but a lot older because my
family like starts with the whole Jews
in Egypt thing, but then spends most of
the stater talking about the civil
rights movement and then ending on of
course the Israeli Palestinian
accomplishments.
Yeah, there you go.
Um, but uh it is interesting. How many
you guys know like secular Jews?
The rest of you know and you just don't
realize it. So, uh I had a Puerto Rican
boyfriend a couple years ago and he was
telling his dad that he had a new
girlfriend. The dad was like, "Oh, nice.
Puerto Rican." And my boyfriend Tom was
like, "No." And dad was like, "Damin?"
He's like, "No." He's like Italian. No.
What is she Jewish? And the dad says,
"Jewish Jewish or Woody Allen Jewish."
actually perfectly captures like a real
it was a real nuance understanding of
Jewish identity, you know, meaning
basically culturally Jewish, but it's
kind of an awkward person to have as
your like
standard, you know, you don't really
want to go there, right? Cuz like
I mean, I don't know if I spell it out,
but
you don't want like a prolific pedophile
to be your go-to person. Thank you. Um,
but uh were you guys upset when you
learned that about Woody Allen? Like I
can barely enjoy this film now, right?
Reminds me of how upset I was when I
learned about London Reenshaw's
politics.
Like I can no longer enjoy trying to
Well,
all right. So, uh, what else? All right,
let's stick to real politics. Real
politique.
How about John Mir Shimemer? All
right, that was just a real that was off
the copy.
All right. Uh, the sad thing is this is
going on my channel.
I just switch it to my chat.
This is maybe I'll this will be a
Patreon only. By the way, please
subscribe to patreon.com/katy
show. Um,
and you'll be and then I don't know.
I'll play something else instead of
this. I'll cut myself out and everyone
else will be in it. I told you I'm
Jewish, so I'm very self-deprecating.
You guys are like, "No, it's actually
appropriately decorating.
It's just observational humor." Um, but
uh what's the deal with, by the way,
what is the deal with everyone who's
like evil getting praised? So,
basically, if you're good like John
Kiryaku, you're punished for being a
whistleblower. Same thing with Julian
Assange. But if you're like a torturer
or the people in the collateral murder
video, you face no justice. All right.
Like, did you guys see Ponda Lisa Rice
lately on Fox News where she condemned
Putin for violating the sovereignty of
an independent country? Like, why did
she condemn it? She mad cuz she wanted
to do it again. She's like jealous.
And then Bush, of course, is a hero
again. I do I do like the dynamic
between Bush and Kanye. It was cute. She
was like his tutor. like she made him
like Iran Iraq flash cards so he could
tell the difference between the
countries and like I think it was really
hard for him because he just mastered
like the U after Q rule and then he had
to constantly deal with the one country
that violates that rule.
Um but I'm I'm I'm surprised that that
Joe Biden isn't more sympathetic to
Julian Assange. I don't know about the
rest of you, but I am surprised because
I thought he'd have more empathy for him
cuz like he understands what it's like
to be locked up cuz of course he was
arrested when he tried to visit Nelson
Mandela.
And like he should get what it's like to
not see daylight for days and days
because of his toiling underground as a
minor,
right?
And he should also understand the
bravery required of Julian Assange who
refuses to back down in the face of
overwhelming odds and state power and
corporate power. Right. And he gets that
because he of course refused to back
down in the face of corn pop.
Really bad dude.
Really bad dude
who he met during his activism in the
civil rights movement. By which we mean
he was a lifeguard.
That was his ML moment was being like um
but honestly Joe if you're watching uh
and I know you are because I'm a huge
fan of my channel. He's actually a sub.
Joe, if you're watching, please like the
stream. But uh if you're watching,
seriously, do the right thing. This is
embarrassing.
Donald Trump went after Assange. your
guy Obama, the constitutional lawyer. I
know you guys are gonna like throw up in
your mouth and stop. Sorry, especially
you, but like just let's say for
argument sake for the libs out there,
you guys like that guy Obama. He's
supposed to be like wise. He's supposed
to be an intellectual guy. He takes the
constitution seriously. and he realized
he couldn't go after Assange because of
the New York Times problem by which he
meant more or less if it was so criminal
for Assange to publish it, it was
obviously criminal for the New York
Times to publish it, the Washington
Post, etc., etc. So Biden, just so you
can go to your dinner parties and
pretend to be this good guy, why don't
you not do the thing that Trump did, why
don't you side with Barack Obama
and um Free Assange because it's the
right thing to do and you should be on
the right side of history and everyone
should be
up in arms about this when Trump did it,
which you should have been because
apparently people cared about the fourth
estate then and you should still care
about it now. So, free the press and
free Julian Assange. And now,
yes,
thank you. Thank you. All right,
that's an applause line, folks.
So, I'm bringing up to the stage someone
who barely needs any uh introduction,
but she is a very inspiring person. She
is also happens to be a good friend of
mine, but even if she weren't a good
friend of mine, I would really be
excited to bring her up. She ran for
president. She speaks truth to power.
She's been very vocal on several issues
including the war in Yemen. Uh Marian
Williamson.
Hello everybody. An honor to be here.
Very moved by you particularly John
Keryaka. Really truly an honor to be
here with you and to hear your words.
Thank you. They went straight to the
heart and were such a truly stunning um
description of the issues that are
involved here. Um we must reclaim uh any
sense of national conscience and to be
in the presence of someone like John who
has really paid such a sacrifice in
order to make a stand for that. And I
think what John was asking all of us to
do is something that we need to think
about very seriously. It seems to me
that the Julian Assange case, the
situation is stuck. It's stuck because
at this point, um, Biden thinks he's got
it handled. Um, we don't make enough
noise to really be an inconvenience. And
until we make enough noise to be a
political inconvenience to Merrick
Garland or, uh, Joe Biden, nothing is
going to change. So, I really want to
um, uh, reiterate what John was saying,
what Randy said. uh whether it's
tomorrow, whether it's at the it is only
to be assumed will happen uh trial in uh
the Eastern District of Virginia, each
of us must do what we can to make more
noise. Um it's a very focused laser beam
type thing and that is as I said
inconveniencing
uh politically uh Garland and Biden and
that's simply by making enough noise.
all of us. The very fact that we're here
means we're already on the case. But at
this point, each of us needs to use
whatever platform we have, whether it's
our Twitter, whether it is our Facebook,
whether it's our Instagram, whether it's
our friends to continue to have the
conversation that the establishment has
been successful at nullifying. It's
really quite extraordinary that the Jake
Tappers, that the Chuck Todds, and that
the Joe Bidens are out there talking
about war crimes done by um uh Vladimir
Putin. Not that he hasn't, and not that
I'm minimizing them, but it was war
crimes done by the US military machine
that were revealed by Julian Assange.
And that's what often gets lost here is
what this man was revealing. This was
torture. These were atrocities. And as
we know, these were murders. These were
murders of people, some of whom were
mentally ill. Many of whom were men
trying to get their women to the
hospital in order to deliver their
babies. And they mistakenly got too
close to checkpoints. They didn't even
know exactly what they were doing. The
classification system was never intended
to be something that the US government
could use simply because information was
inconvenient to have revealed. In order
for a document to be classified legally,
the government needs to be able to prove
that this is classified because it would
be a danger to US security for this
information to be revealed. But now
millions of documents every year are
classified for no other reason than the
government does not want us to know
what's in them. And it takes people like
John um Keryaku and Julian Assange to
say the government might not want you to
know but you must know or there is no
greater threat to the security of the
United States than that we take that
route to police state and government
secrecy.
And so to be in the presence of John and
to be talking about Julian, I think it's
important for all of us to ask ourselves
given what they have done, what can we
do? And I think that that it's it's so
interesting because what the system has
been able to do, we're talking here
about our need to inconvenience the
system, but they've created a situation
where we're considered a social
inconvenience to bring it up. Are you
gonna bring up Julian Assange again?
We're We're at dinner. We're having a
dinner party. Are you really gonna bring
up Julian Assange again? I think
particularly, if I may say so, I think
it's particularly difficult for a woman
when they start rolling their eyes and
are you talking about that again? We
know how you are. And it's so important
on a night like tonight that we commit
to ourselves that next time somebody
says, "Oh my god, are you going to talk
about Julian Assange again?" Please
respond by saying, "Have you heard the
one about Julian Assange? Have you ever
heard the one about Julian Assange? Do
you know that it has absolutely nothing
to do with Hillary Clinton's emails? Do
you know that this was in 2010? It was
way before anything Hillary Clinton's
emails. Do you know that this has to do
with murders? Do you know that this has
to do with atrocities? Do you know that
this has to do with torture? Do you know
what this means? If the government can
can shut stuff up like this, do you know
what it means that the US government
doesn't cover for the US defense
department when it is when it is
perpetrating atrocities like this? And
do you know what it means about us as
people that we refuse to shut up about
it? And then if they say, "Oh my god, do
we have to talk about this one more
time?" All I can ask you, all of us is
please that we leave here tonight
committed. Damn right. We're going to
talk about it one more time.
That was powerful.
I follow
that great once again. Marian
Williamson, you can see why they push
her off the uh debates in 2020. We can't
have her up there, Josh. But we're
behind you. I don't know if you're
running for office again, but people
should get behind you. If you do, I know
we may get some support from the
people's party. I know Nick Bronn is
here tonight.
We need a voice like that speaking
nationally. Thank you. And it took a lot
of guts and a lot of courage to do what
you did in 20120 during those debates.
Nobody. Even Bernie Sanders
was saying, "Boy, she's way out there on
the other side. She's too far to the
left. I can't even talk like this about
Julian SL.
Leave it to her." And then, you know, I
I got to consider my position as the
head of some committee.
I've got a committee. I got to I'm
almost 80 years old. Why should I not
sell out? No.
All right, I'm serious. I saw you in
2020. I said, "Wow, where did she come
from?"
And uh the Department of Peace, she
comes up with this idea. What a great
idea. Marian Williamson said if she were
president, she would not the Department
of Defense, which is the Department of
War is what it is. It was the Department
of Peace. What a great idea that is. And
uh let's think about that. And once
again, give her another big round of
applause.
And to Katie Halper,
when Katie helper, usually you take her
off as an MC. I said, Katie, you'll
bring up Marian Williamson because you
know her well, but the right thing to do
was to like bring you up and then take
you off and give you a big round of
applause. So, that was uh very
self-sacrificing. Thank you very much.
Uh once again, Katie Halper, we're are
on her
channel on YouTube.
All right, so we have uh we're we're
continuing. The bar is still open.
Please keep this place uh open. I want
to thank once again the Tavern in uh
because you know they're going to take
heat for this. This is an employee This
is an employeeowned
incredible
institution. It really
must
acknowledge Fritzy Cohen who is the
matriarch today.
I came here with Sam Husini who didn't
show up tonight because he didn't have a
mask and and
that was thick enough. Hi Sam, I know
you're watching but he brought me here
like four months ago. We were looking
for a place to do this standup for songs
and he brought me here and Fritzy said
yes of course. And then Dave Ruby, who's
a general manager and uh one of the
great uh individuals that I've met in my
lifetime. He's back there pacing.
Dave,
because there are are a couple of
crazies who tried to sneak in tonight.
Dave has got it. He's got it all set.
And uh give thank you Dave for all that
you've done in support of this and all
the employees here who are owners. This
is a Can you imagine this beautiful this
beautiful historic
hotel and restaurant and in is
employeeowned.
This should be the role model for every
place across the country.
This is
I just want to tip my hat to the uh the
Amazon workers union for that historic
victory.
You know what solidarity now? The one
that uh Pete Singer said.
Solidarity forever.
[Music]
Of course he does. Solidarity forever.
Who knows the words?
[Music]
power gater anywhere beneath the sun.
Yet the force on earth is we
strength of the union that makes us
strong
[Music]
forever
foreverary
forever.
All right. Thank you, man. That was
really wonderful.
And I know that's a big thing for my
good friend here, Chuck Slackin, who's
with NYC Free Assange, who's been
working forever uh as a uh as the union
head in New York City with the postal
workers union, and they just got finally
uh something very big and even Chuck
Schumer supported it. So, uh, you got
everybody supporting Canada. So, there
cannot be, what is it, Chuck?
Service reform act of 2022 was signed
into law passed Wednesday and it only
took us 16 years to get it back.
Congratulations, Chuck. I know you've
been working on it for a long time.
All right, so we're going to bring up
we're going to keep that. We have We
still have Lee Camp. We still have Media
Benjamin coming up. We still have
Margaret Ratner, counselor, coming up.
We still have Lucy uh Murphy coming up
and uh probably somebody else, but um uh
and I'm going to announce the event
tomorrow morning in front of the British
consulate,
one of the US's great colonies, the
British consulate.
They should have a old glory on top of
that continent. Uh that's coming up
tomorrow 10. and then at 2:00 in front
of uh the Department of Injustice. All
right. Uh so we're going to bring up
we're we got to get some laughs here. We
still have a couple more comedians. So
uh let's have a good time. Uh this is
another individual that's now no longer
with RT since they were censored and
thrown off the air during this new what
is really they had 1919. They had their
first red scare and they had the 50s or
the second red scare and the
McCarthyism. It's like Russia is no
longer the Soviet Union, but we have a
third red scare going on. And uh the
victims have been stations like RT that
give a different point of view. And uh
one of the point
the correct one you can see.
Yes, it you're right. All right. I kind
of like I know I middled that. All
right. I middled that for the CIA that's
in the back of the room writing down my
resume. All right. Remember I used to do
my acting for the US embassy in 86 87 88
in Nicaragua. The only great crowd I
ever had was
7 o'clock in the morning after drinking
bootleg Florida Kanye and having to uh
entertain all the peace groups there.
All right, they're the only ones who
understood my impression of General
Singal.
Nobody knows much from who single was
and Elliot Abrams who changed his name
to Tony Blink.
All right. So, we're going to bring up
right now really he's been at every one
of these events and he's a tremendous
political satist. Would you please
welcome Jaffer Cox?
He's ready to laugh.
Thanks Randy for that intro. The RT
intro. This next guy, he's unemployed as
[__] Just got laid off.
It's fine. I'm not bitter about it.
This is uh it's good to be here. Give a
round of applause to yourselves coming
out.
This is great.
I am always genuinely very honored to be
here and a part of these amazing
lineups. Um this is uh this is the model
minority part of the show. Um,
y'all remember that in the '90s they
would call every Asian person in America
a model minority? How racist was that uh
to other minorities, right? Just like
that the the the racism in the US is
very advanced, right? Uh it's very
nuanced. That's mind-blowing. them. It's
like, look, if you got if you got to be
a minority in this country, if you have
to be a minority, do it with some grace.
All right? Do it like them. Look at
them. They study. They're quiet. They
don't talk during the movies.
Who's ready to laugh? Huh? You know,
I don't know. Um,
you know,
I um I was a model minority.
I'm Pakistani.
I was a model minority until around
9/11. That went out the window
real quick. They were like, "Oh, this is
not model minority behavior." I was
like, "You're right. You're right. I'm
sorry. Take me off the list. Put me on
the new list. I'll go on my list." Yeah.
I remember after 911, I was like in
seventh grade and there was this kid who
didn't like me. So, he was trying to
hurt my feelings and he was like, "Your
people did this to us." And before I
could say anything, my buddy Phil jumped
in. Phil was like, "Actually, Joffer is
from Pakistan. His country had nothing
to do with 9/11." And then I had to jump
in like, "Actually,
you know, Osama gets all the credit."
What was he? He was just an investor.
That's all he was. He was just a
financeier of vengeance. Uh the man,
y'all know who the man credited with the
architect of 911. Khali Shank Muhammad
currently in Guantanamo Bay. a Pakistani
man. So, let's give credit where credit
is due. Okay? We're out here. We're
making moves. We're doing stuff. We're
model minorities. We're making a
difference.
Look, Muslims, um, you know, we're not
terrorists. Um, because there's actually
no such thing as a terrorist, which I
know sounds like something a terrorist
would say, but uh, look, you'll know
what I mean. I I don't have to explain
it to this audience. You know, we're
terrorist. Very, it's a political term.
Every country in the world, their
enemies are terrorists. They're never
terrorist. We're never terrorists,
right? Like, and it's the UN has always
struggled trying to come up with an
actual like specific like precise
definition for terrorism. Probably
because every time they come up with
one, the CIA is just like, that's not
going to work for us.
Awkward. You know, we don't want people
bringing up, you know, Guatemala or
Brazil or Venezuela or Cuba or Libya or
Iran or Lebanon or
Sudan or Somalia or JFK. Who's that JFK?
Who's that? Use that JK. Don't bring up
JFK, please. Sorry.
Weird. Weird that you said that.
The only way uh the the UN could come up
with a definition for terrorism that the
US would like be excited about it would
have to be extremely specific right like
look here at the UN we condemn terrorism
obviously and terrorism is like we all
know anytime anyone anywhere anytime
anywhere 19 dudes who don't import or
drink beer board a plane planes
very important terrorist not fighter
jets those are Commercial airlines.
Write this down. Anytime 19 dudes who
pray five times a day, book United
on a Tuesday,
Billy 7:47. And I know this is where the
laughter deties down. Audiences at this
point are just like, "This brown guy
knows a lot about 911.
That's kind of my vibe. I'm the 911 guy.
Uh, that's what I'm trying to do." And
just for the record, know that this is
the tame version of me. All right. This
is me. People don't know who I am, so I
got to kind of warm people up. But one
day, I'm going to be famous, okay? And
when I'm famous, my comedy will be free
and liberated and insufferable. Okay? I
I will have the lowest Rotten Tomato
rating of all time. Just confused
reviews. Just like, I guess it was
comedy, but he did a 10-minute bit on
the application process to ISIS, and it
was alarmingly detailed.
Yes, I like to have frightening comedy.
Um
we uh you know recently we had we had a
real low moment in our war on terror
which I really enjoyed. Um we uh we
recently killed like the newest leader
of ISIS and it makes sense. I remember
waking up that morning just like why do
I feel so safe? Is it is it working? Um
and uh you know Biden came up and did
his like he got to do his big serious
Joe press conference dramatic press like
serious time. America joke time. And um
and he did this dramatic press
conference and uh no one gave a [__] It
was beautiful. Uh I love it. There's
people out there who like Joe Biden, but
every citizen of this country has to
admit that that man cannot read a room,
right? That's not not his strong suit
public speaking. Um it's unfortunate. Uh
but I look he gave this dramatic press
conference. I understand why he was
excited for the press conference, right?
He was thinking about Obama. Remember
Obama's press conference? He got to be
like, "Oh, we got Osama." Everyone was
like happy and cheered. Even Trump got
to be like, "We got Abu Bakr al-Badi,
right? OG uh leader of ISIS." This new
leader of ISIS. I don't even know the
guy's name. Okay, I don't know his name.
And I know Abu Bakr al-Badi, right? I
know my [__] I show love, right? Y'all
know that about me. I'm pretty sure Joe
Biden didn't even know this [__]
guy's name. Okay, I watched the entire
press conference. He didn't say his name
a single time. He just kept calling him
like a coward and a dog. We got America.
Don't worry. Squad Joe here being
serious. We got We got We got the
coward. We got the dog. We curse the
cowardly dog. That's what I call him.
That's what I call Well, of course. Of
course. I know. Of course. Jojo knows
his name. What's his name? Abu Baba.
Boooo. Aiz. I'm sorry. Look, the point
is
America, the guy that you didn't know
was alive is no longer alive. See that
sound like Joe's on the case. And his
wife is like, "Who you talking to, Joe?
We're at lunch right now."
All right. That's
comedy. Um,
I think that's comedy. Um,
we're now now we're uh pivot now we're
doing a new uh we're doing a war on
domestic terrorism now aka a war on
white people terrorism. Um, which you
know before was a war on Muslim terror
terrorism. Let's uh recap that real
quick. Uh that was uh led to the murder
of over a million people. the
destabilization of the Middle East,
which led to a refugee crisis, which in
turn led to a rise led to a rise of
anti-migrant racist sentiment around the
world, which in turn is fueling a rise
of neopascism, which we're all dealing
with today. And
in 8th grade, me and my friends went to
school dressed as ninjas. And the police
officer stepped into the office cuz he
thought I was dressed as al-Qaeda
on dress like your superhero day. Yeah,
you can laugh at that. Some parts of the
war on terror are kind of lighthearted
and that was one of the funnier parts.
Um, but look, that was a war on Muslim
terror. Okay, now we're in a war on
domestic terror. I don't know. I don't
really see a war. Look, I'm I'm I'm
seeing more of a kurfuffle on domestic
terrorism. And look, I'm Muslim. I'm
petty. I want to see a war. All right,
I'll be honest. I Where's the war?
Where's the war? Show me a war. I want
to see Here's what I'm see. I want to
see uh two of these insurrectionists. We
found out that they got family from
Poland. So, our government bombs the
[__] out of France, right? That's what I
want to see. I want to see some
consistency. Okay. I want to see I want
to see a panel on CNN where the topic of
discussion is, is Southern Baptism
really a religion of peace?
On our panel today, we have Breza Osman,
Raja Khi, and John. I know on Southern
Baptism before, I wanted to see Guantano
Bay shut down forever. I'm against
torture. Not anymore. Repurpose it.
Repurpose it. Get Get the brown
terrorists out. White terrorists in. No
shoes allowed inside. That is torture
for white people. That would be a first
rule. I want to see
I want I want to see uh I want to see a
white kid get in trouble for dressing
like a terrorist or dress like a
superhero. He's going to the office all
pissed off. Like I'm not an
interruptionist. I just like wearing
camo. God.
[Music]
I mean, I know, you know, I'm joking. We
all know the war war on domestic
terrorism is not a good thing. Uh, but
thankfully, no one really gives a [__]
No one's excited about it. There's only
one group of people excited about the
war on domestic terror, and uh, that is
white liberals. God damn, dude. Anytime
on the news they call a white person a
terrorist, white liberal, they cream
their pants. They get so happy. They're
like, "Yes, we're terrorists, too.
Hello. Come get us. Hide that vote for
Trump. Arrest him, FBI.
Dude, white liberal women, they've all
cut ties to the Republican dads. They
don't talk to them anymore. It's like,
talk to your dad, all right? He raised
you. He loves you. He co-signed your
lease. It's the least it's the least you
can do, dude. Um, I don't know what's
happening with white people and their
like the last insurrectionist that got
arrested, you like his uh his son
snitched on him.
That's how we got and people applauded
that. That's tragic. Okay, my my dad is
a Muslim Republican. He's a psycho. He's
a zip out Muslim Republican. He might do
a [__] jihad against Biden, but I
will I would I would never ride out my
dad. Okay, I love my dad. He raised me.
What is happening with white family
structure in this country that they're
ratting out their own damn parents? This
is tragic to me. It just shows that
Bernie Mack was right. Okay, white
people, you got to beat your kids. You
got to
proud of white folk beat the damn kids.
All right, they're out here at now their
own family. It's a damn shame. Um, but
here's where I would normally end the
bit with like for normal audiences. I'm
like, but on a serious note, white
people don't trust the FBI. Don't answer
your culture, but I know y'all uh y'all
don't need to hear that. So, um I'll
I'll I'll just say this. Um you know, uh
you you have heard and you will hear
people much smarter and better equipped
than me. uh say uh you know great things
about this cause. Um so I don't really
have much to add to that, but this is a
cause we should all be supporting and
I'm really glad we're all here and that
this is happening and I'm happy to be a
part of it. So thank you everyone.
[Applause]
Everybody having a good time tonight?
Yeah,
we are here to free Julian Assange.
Right.
I hope people will join
Comrade Misty.
And Ulysa says Grant here.
General Long Street. I don't know.
Great beard.
You don't need a mask. You got that
beard.
No, I want to talk to you. I want to
bust your balls. He and I bust each
other's balls for the last couple of
months.
This is Dave Ruby who is the general
manager. All right.
And one of the owners of this place
because of Fritzy Cohen that this has
made his pack all the time. And this is
the place if you are supporting Julian
Assange. This is the uh ground zero.
We're going to be working out of here.
And Gabriel Shipton, Julian's brother
will be back here. He will be staying
here. So will uh Julian's father, uh
John Shipton be staying here because
they know the commitment. Fritzy Cohen
over there. I know you want me to sing
Jimmy Kagny, but you know I
cuz you're the only one that knows. Let
me ask you this.
Yes.
Who is ready to sign up for a jihad
against?
Somebody's got some petition. Paula, do
you have a petition?
Davis is like
Paula, do you have a petition? A jihad
against what?
I don't want to say that here. They'll
find a way to like throw me in with Bin
Laden and I'll be in prison for 20
[__] years in Guantanamo.
Remember the words of Jesse
We're supposed to have three people.
Don't let her say it.
I'm talking about a jihad. I mean, I'm
not talking about a specific group of
people who has been accused of doing.
I think that was Keith.
[Music]
That was in the back.
But what I'm saying is this is that
we need
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Let her finish what she
has to say. I don't censor anybody,
especially the one that let us do this
here tonight in the last four events.
It's pretty
suggesting that jihadists have just
gotten a bad name. What I'm saying is
that maybe that's something that we
people who need to protect the first
amendment need to form something. Maybe
we can call it something different to go
after the real fascists in this country
who are against Julian and they're in
our government. you know, and uh and we
just want to finish the show.
No.
Did she finish her?
Yes. Would you stop? She and I have a
good rapport. Okay.
I know. Anyway, but you know, I am I I
am who I am
and I and that's what Papey said.
Well, and I am who I am.
No, I agree with you, Fritzy. I think
that we should
There may be a better way of saying it.
Yes. I think you should first actually
but you know but
are you her PR person?
Yeah.
Let her talk. All right.
I haven't heard it in haven't you had
five drinks
like tonight. All right. So please
of
I'm joking. Please. I'm a comic.
I used to be.
I've lost my sense of humor. All right.
All right. You're going to have a debate
with me.
All right. So, what?
All right. I'm through. But
All right. We'll talk about it later,
Fritz. We're going to have an open mic
when the show's over. Anybody can get up
here and say what they want. It's going
to be like uh what do you call
on a Jaffer? He He
Do you like him?
Oh, I do. Yeah.
He encouraged me to speak out.
Yeah.
But apparently that was not correct.
All right. Do you want her as your
sidekick?
All right. Always nice to have a chorus
if you sing in tune. All right. How you
doing, brother?
You're the best. Steve Jones once again.
All right. We are here tonight for
Julian Assange.
We here tomorrow once again 10 in the
morning. I'll be there in front of the
Where is that? Uh, comrade Misty.
British ambition.
I know that, but where is it? 3100
Massachusetts Avenue.
I thought it was inside the White House.
All right. So, it's 3100 Massachusetts
Avenue. And then at 2:00 in front of uh
Merrick Garland, who's sick right now,
as if he wasn't already sick, but he's
got physical ailments and he may not
show up.
All right. And who else? And and so you
got a petition, Paula.
I got to keep the comedy going here.
No, we're going. We're good.
All right. We're good. All right. We
we'll do it later. We still have a
couple acts. And then before we go, we
have a wonderful uh singer at the end,
Lucy Murphy. Before that, the um one of
the great heroes legally of my lifetime
for the last 50 years is going to who
the only one that I know who knows Julie
Assange
really well in this room who's visited
him 50 times and has been a legal
adviser and saw him at Bill Morris.
That's Margaret Bradford Cutsler. Give
her a round of applause.
She came all the way from New York City.
All the way from New York City. We broke
down this morning and it was the first
time where I didn't offer 95 get off on
the exit to the Baltimore airport. All
right. If you listen to if you listen to
that Siri, go to the right, go to the
left, go to and you end up, you know, in
Cleveland. All right. So, I just
followed the signs today and got here on
time. So, I don't need that [__] GPS
anymore. I'm serious. Don't drive to
that.
I mean, Lewis and Clark made it all the
way to Utah without a GPS.
GPS.
All right, listen. Are you going to
get Can you give her a couple of
thumbs?
It's all
It's just truth. Sorry.
Is that a bad thing?
It's a bad thing that you're slowing
down the show. All right. All right.
It's okay. You can say what you want.
But
therefore,
she's giving energy.
She'll be like Native American.
I love it. The fact that you're helping
this place out.
at that board 13.
Never mind. All right.
All right. So, uh, one of the great
activists that I've met in my lifetime,
I met her through Tony Newman from, uh,
way back in San Francisco in the in the
80s. And she was, I think, running for
she was like sitting in a tree. Were you
sitting in a tree? I like in a redwood
up there in Sequoia where I used to go
when I was a kid. And the greatest stunt
that I've ever seen over the last 20
years was at the RNC convention in 2004
when Code Pink interrupted uh was it
Dick Cheney or when who was it?
All of them.
It was rocket
5 years, six years including his head,
his shoulders and now above his head. I
remember that. That was when George Bush
was there. We're fighting against cicas.
America is fighting cicas. We got We got
I can only protect this country by
hiding hiding our freedom. We're we're
we're fighting against uh cicas.
[Music]
I used to do, you know, I started out
doing Nixon in 1972
when I first started out 50 years ago as
a comedian. It was Nixon. Uh, Denn Bush.
It was Ford, but it was really just
kiss. By the way, it's Kissinger's
birthday on Thursday. He turned 700. So,
let's give a
He turned 700 and uh there's no room in
the reason why he hasn't died cuz
there's no [__] room in hell for him.
They have to build a parallel hell for
Kissinger alone. And then it was Jim
Aarta was for four years and he was all
right. Then it was Reagan and I yes he
was there and for the next uh whatever
and then then after Reagan it was George
Bush senior. We are not at war with the
people of Iraq. We are at war with the
Iraqi people.
Yeah. And then he did his Churchill
speech when it was all over. Never have
so few killed so many for so few that
have so much. Thank you very much.
[Music]
That was Bill Clinton for 8 years and he
did what he did. He killed 500,000
people in in Iraq with the sanctions and
uh what he did with NATO. You have to
know about NATO and Yugoslavia and all
that [__] Then he got [__] by Amy
Goodman and he got all upset by what?
All right. So, he's gone. And then it
was uh George
Bush Dub. God bless America. America is
the greatest nation in the land. He
actually said that
Texas is 50th in the country in
education, but we didn't drop back to 51
or 52.
the top 50 part.
I'm not going to do the rest of them.
All right. So, uh coming up and and so
uh this was a great event and uh I love
media for what she did at the Republican
National Convention. She's going to
bring up uh our headline comic uh and so
give her a big round of applause.
Should
I tell the one joke I know they do in
politics? It's like a kids joke.
You got to laugh. Okay. It's the one
where the bear and the rabbit are taking
a crap in the forest and the bear says
to the rabbit, "You have any problem
with [__] sticking to your fur?" And the
rabbit says, "No." So the bear grabs a
rapid wipes his neck.
Okay, now to Afghanistan.
So I just came back from Afghanistan and
it really makes me think about Julian
Assange because I went to Afghanistan
for the first time 20 years ago when the
US was bombing Afghanistan. started out
the shock, you know, and we were told
that these were now, remember, precision
bombs. Remember that?
Yeah. Precision bombs.
And that there weren't going to be
civilian casualties. So, I went over
with a group of there were four of us
women. And uh where's Staffer? We went
into Pakistan first. There went into
Pashawer. You know Pashawer? Yeah. It's
a wild place. went through the uh crazy
mountains to get into Kbble and found
these streams of civilians whose loved
ones had just been killed by US
precision bombs.
And we thought, you know, what are we
going to do about this? Kids who didn't
have parents anymore. Uh uh widows who
had no money to feed their kids. People
who were desperate to begin with and now
we're just totally totally impoverished.
Not a penny. So we went back to the
United States. We went to the US
government. We said, "First of all, you
got to stop killing civilians. And
second of all, the ones you've killed,
you got to compensate them."
So they said, "You're crazy. These are
precision bombs. We don't kill
civilians." That was in the old days.
Well, we fought and we fought and fought
and finally we had the Afghan War
Diaries thanks to Wikileaks.
Thank you.
And what did the Afghan war diary show?
They had first they released about
90,000 memos that show thousands and
thousands of civilian casualties. And
then they released uh maybe you wrote
it, John, a CIA manual about how to
convince the American public that this
is actually a good war. And then they
released documents about
um you know the uh death by container.
Uh the younger ones here probably don't
remember that but this was when a bunch
of Taliban like thousands of them
surrendered and they were put in these
metal containers to transport them and
then they were either just suffocated to
death or they were shot at through the
containers and it could have been up to
2,000 prisoners of war. That's actually
not allowed. prisoners of war. Uh they
even released to show they were even
handed memos from jihadists. There were
like a thousand handwritten memos
uh that um released by Wikileaks.
And so all of these materials in total
were over 300,000
documents related to Afghanistan. It was
amazing. Now, for us, it helped us go to
the American government and force them
to create a compensation fund for Afghan
victims. Now, you know, we could talk
about what was the life of an Afghan
victim worth because it wasn't very
worth very much according to the US
government. But thanks to those Afghan
war diaries, we could prove that there
were thousands and thousands of civilian
victims. But more important than that,
it changed the perception of the Afghan
war.
It changed perception from the Afghan
war being the good war and all we had to
do is send in more more troops, just
another surge and we could have won that
war to one that showed that it was
indeed a quagmire and we had to figure
out how to get the hell out of here. And
so we owe a lot to Julian Assange
for helping us to understand what was
really going on in Afghanistan, what our
government was really doing in
Afghanistan, for exposing all the lies
of our government, exposing all the
deaths. And now I know we're not allowed
to talk about Ukraine, but I'm only
going to say it because the American
people are caring about civilian deaths
because they see it every day on the TV
screens. And if we had a media that
would have shown us all of the deaths in
Afghanistan, we wouldn't have needed
Wikileaks to teach us.
And now I want to bring up somebody who
embodies both comedy and truthtelling.
And I loved watching him on
RT. And it's a terrible shame that RT is
not the venue where we can see him right
now. But we still have many ways to
still watch Lee Camp who makes us laugh.
[Applause]
[Music]
that I It's an honor to share a stage
with Media, a woman who's been dragged
down more rooms by security that walked
out of
the incredible No, But seriously, it's
so good to be on this stage with like
heroes of mine. Randy Kico cause Russia
game. I don't know if you watch MSNBC,
but he [__] did it.
This is a man. He was the go between
between Julie Assange and Roger Stone.
Rachel said,
this is a man who thinks phone apps is
how you order appetizers from a car.
He caused Russia Gates. This is the only
No, but seriously, I honestly the only
comedian to do Johnny Carson and lose
gigs
because he called the Secretary of State
Eva Braun or something.
So, I'm not I'm not kidding. An honor to
be on the stage with with all these
wonderful people for such an incredible
cause, such an important cause, and uh
and and it's great to be up here. Uh, I
guess I'm now the the most censured
comedian in America who hasn't sexually
assaulted anyone.
All right, never mind. L just got a
Grammy. The most censured comedian in
America, period.
It's more you're more censored if you're
anti-war
than for all the other [__] that these
people do. No, but it's in the in a in a
single day. Well, so in three days and
the TV shows are cancelled, all the all
the old episodes deleted off of YouTube,
podcast deleted off of Spotify. But in
America, we have freedom of press.
We have freedom of of speech, right?
That's what we have here. No, it's it's
it's utter horseshit, but it's it's
exciting to be here. This is such such
an important cause. Julian Assange, a
man who should have [__] statues
built for him. I mean, if that's what
statues are supposed to be in our
society, right? The people we look up
to, the people that show us how to
behave, what we should be, what we
should aim to be, if we could just if if
if we had the spine they had, that's
what statues should be, right? Instead,
in this country, if you look at the
statues and you really statistically
speaking, apparently
there are more impressive and
accomplished
horses in this country than women.
Something can be funny and true at the
same time. Like you guys were like, I
want to laugh, but [__] [__]
All really, if you don't laugh at
everything I say, that's kind of funny,
but also that's everything I have. So,
we're in trouble. All right. Well,
actually, here's something else. This is
for people not liking my other [__]
The other day, I saw a sushi restaurant
where the sushi goes around on a
conveyor belt and you pick what you
want. I think that's how bears view
hiking trails.
Take your time on some of these.
All right, let's let's go to I thought
let's go to the real colony material,
right? The our newspapers, our our
lovely legacy press. This is the highly
respected Wall Street Journal
from from this past week. Top headline
leaders demand war crime probe. So that
should say war criminals demand war
crime probe, right? You're going to
what? American and NATO leaders for a
war crime probe. That's going to Jeffrey
Dmer for restaurant recommendations.
Charlie Sheen to teach us etiquette, you
know, and [__] Will Smith.
Other headline, Tesla chief Musk
disclosed he just bought a 9% stake of
Twitter. And and people are like, "Oh,
this is good." Cuz he's talking about
not censoring Twitter. And people are
like, "This is great." It's like, "No, a
sociopath
just bought a large part of the public
discourse
and don't celebrate that shit." And they
are all billionaires sociopaths. All
right? Every goddamn one.
not hero.
You cannot be a billionaire and not be a
sociopath. If someone owns a billion of
anything else and they had a billion
cats or a billion shoes or a billion
collectible cookie jars, you wouldn't
go, "Wow, really impressive. What is
your trick? How did you do it?" You
know, that guy's a [__] lunatic.
So, what's the different with a billion
pieces of paper?
And I know you're like, well, the
difference it's actually worse because a
billionaire could give half of their
billion things to like poor people and
change their lives, which you couldn't
do with half of your billion cats. I
mean, I guess you could change them for
the weirder, but you couldn't
you couldn't help people.
They're all sociopaths, and we need to
start remembering that. All right. Next
headline, invasion drives countries to
green energy, but not yet.
Yeah, if we just had more [__] war,
we could save the planet. That's what we
need.
Uh, all right. This is a New York Times.
Excellent newspaper. Excellent.
Excellent. You know, oh, by the way, for
anyone under 30, I know you might not
know what these are. These are you
people used to buy these and hold them
and read them and they wave them and
around
and they and and you know it was a
thing. It's like it's like if you had a
bunch of iPads all glued together and
you
New York Times I don't know if you know
this 70% of the distributor distribution
of New York Times now uh sales of New
York Times is for uh proof of life
photos. That's
That was for poor people. John Keryaku
liked it. John Keryaku. All right. If he
laughs, you all better [__] laugh.
Jesus.
This makes your time in prison for you
people. And you're not laughing if he
finds one.
So, this headline says, "Hundreds
missing and tons of rubble to clear in
Ukraine." Uh, so first of all,
apparently New York Times cares about
people harmed by war. That's
interesting. Look at that. But also, uh,
yeah, turns out war is disgusting.
That's what that headline should read.
War is [__] It's all [__] Where?
Like, but they show photos of the rubble
and the dead and everything. Where were
those photos in Syria and Iraq and
[__]
All of a sudden, New York Times is like,
"Turns out war is awful."
Uh, then lower down on the page, Darthur
trial at the HEG.
Uh, the International Criminal Court,
uh, which is a criminal court for
prosecuting war criminals who are black.
So, I don't even know, was it 99%
of the ones they prosecuted have been
black. And the US actually has Congress
passed what is lovingly called the
Netherland Netherlands Invasion Act
where if they were to take one of our
soldiers or one of our people and put
them on trial, the ICT, we would invade
the Netherlands.
What?
Yes, we passed that through Congress.
All right. That is going to be a [__]
interesting invasion. I mean, them
trying to defend themselves on their
windmill powered bicycles from throwing
wooden shoes at us. This is going to be
a hell of a fight.
Another headline, boom time for vertical
farms
because we don't have seasons anymore.
That's the part they forgot. They're
just excited. Vertical parks doing
really well cuz everything outside's
dying. Babe, you want to mention that?
No. No. Not so much. Not in the New York
Times.
Some of these are bummers, folks. Some
of these are bummer.
Exp. This is uh still New York Times
experts believe hackers are targeting
Ukraine with misinformation efforts.
This is the New York Times uh pissed off
that they have competition
the misinformation effort. They're like
[__]
And those people don't even have to
print it on the pieces of paper.
Uh and then this is uh maybe still New
York Times. Germany finds it hard to
drop Russian energy. I love this is kind
of like, you know, standard like, you
know, it'll talk about Russian war
crimes and stuff in there. So, it's like
a standard anti-Russian article, but
still they're using the euphemism for
planetary death fluid. It's energy.
Germany's finding it hard to quit
energy. Energy sounds like, you know,
suburban what suburban moms have at like
a jazzer size [__] class. They got a
lot of energy, a lot of pep. No, it's
planetary death fluid. That's what
they're trying to quit.
And I think we're all addicted to it.
Better go back to these.
I have a voodoo doll of myself at home
that I treat quite well.
[Laughter]
Well, let's see. I'll just do a few more
minutes here. They they What? The Biden
is adding funding to the police.
Yeah.
More more police cuz that's really going
to fix things. It's just more of these
[__] idiots with guns.
Yeah.
And and really part of the solution is
please everybody stop calling the police
for nonsense. You do not need men with
guns inserted into any situation almost
ever. Almost. People call people act
like it's their daddy. They're like the
music is too loud. comes sending you're
sending idiots with guns into a
situation because a Bruno Mars did was a
little loud. Like that's that's like
calling a guy with napal because there's
a light smell of ass coming from next
door. It's [__] insanity.
Honestly, and and they they are they're
maniacs that most of them they don't
[__] know how to deal with half the
situation that they are thrust into. and
and they're a lot of them are drugged up
on steroids and all the numbers the
estimates are that 25% of all urban
police are filled with steroids and
guess what roid rage fits really well if
you look at police brutality oh poor
decision making quick to violence all
these things like oh interesting and we
don't even test them we don't even test
it after they [__] harm someone we
don't test them like we we test Olympic
athletes to see
Just to see if someone legitimately
jumped over things really quick. Okay.
Oh, you went really fast over those
sticks.
See if you did it legitimately cuz
otherwise you're going to [__] hell.
But we don't cop like why are we like I
mean with the Olympics we're like wow
you threw that stick really far. Let's
see if you did. Why the cops? We know
like, "Wow, you threw that grandma
really far. Let's see if you did it
legitimately. Let's see if that's a new
record or not."
Did you know that if you took your lungs
and spread them out flat, they would
cover a tennis court?
But you'd probably lose the match.
True story, googly.
All right, I'll wrap up with this. We
need to we need to expand and it's part
of the reason I'm I'm I'm thrilled to be
here. I'm thrilled to be with so many of
you. So many of you I kind of know or I
know a little bit and you do such
impressive stuff and and it's like we
have to expand the step one of this of
of of changing this world is to expand
the debate which really all of you are
part of and don't debate within this
little Randy mentioned earlier this
little [__] allowable thought on
corporate media which of course we've
been you know Randy lost gigs I've been
purged from media like they want you in
this little box of allowable debates
that's what it is they have you know
Even when they have a debate, it's like
someone being like, "We're going to bomb
Syria right now." And then someone right
here being like, "We're going to bomb
the next week." And they're like,
"That's the whole debate. That's all
there can be." And so, you got to expand
the debate. Don't debate about whether
there's too much corporate spending in
our elections. Debate whether there
should be corporations at all in this
[__] country.
Don't debate about whether someone
should be locked away for life for their
third drug charge. Debate about whether
there should be drug charges at all
or whether it should be a health problem
instead of a crime problem. Don't debate
about about whether you know dropping
our drone bombs is killing too many
innocent civilians. Debate about whether
we should be at war at all. Have that
debate.
Don't debate about whether our schooling
system is creating too many dumb kids.
Debate about whether there should be
dumb kids at all.
They should be released into the woods
is a creative [__] Lord of the Flies.
Thank you guys so much.
[Applause]
Wow, that was great. They can't. Can you
imagine that? I can't find him on
YouTube. I can't find him on RT. I can't
find him on Spotify.
They have mummified the voice of Lee
Camp. And what did you hear tonight? Can
you imagine?
that that's happening right now in this
country that the voice of Lee Camp is
silenced
along with Jaffer Khan uh along with
John F. O'Donnell along with George
Galloway along with uh the great Ashen
Ratanzi awardwinning uh
journalist and Chris
Chris Hedges. Yes,
you're right. Thank you. Abby Martin.
I'm Abby Martin is like, you know,
they what let's
look at it, man. It's it's amazing that
that we can't hear any descent in this
country.
The only thing we get is
John, that guy Jim Skioto,
and the other guy, Jim Acasta. That's
it. That's the news.
Come on. You got Rachel Matt out. Come
on.
Well, you know, she's a road scholar and
you know,
road scholar that decided that she likes
to drink Lawrence O'Donnell at 30 Rock
at that bottom because I've done I've
done uh MSNBC 11 times. The only thing
they wanted to talk to me about was this
whole [__] about Russia Gate and
Roger Stone and and Julian Assange.
There was nothing ever there. Can you
imagine Julian Assange saying to me,
"Hey, look, I got this great stuff
that's coming out. Would you do me a
favor? Pass it to Roger Stone.
You all right? Really, it's pass this to
Roger Stone. I want him to get so it
undermines the surprise of my uh release
of these documents." I mean, it's just
so [__] ridiculous. But they ran with
it and for a couple of years and now
he's uh he continues. They brought up
especially this nutcase empty will this
empty suit empty will uh that is
promoting this ridiculous
fairy tale that there was something
between Megan Rogerstone and Margaret
Ratner Counselor. There was nothing. Uh
but they uh continue to smear Julian
Assange. That's one way. Uh, and because
they want to quiet the guy. But at any
rate, what I'm going to do right now, we
still have Lucy Murphy's going to sing
and then we may have a couple of
speakers afterwards as the we got to
close down the live stream, but uh,
right now I'm going to bring up someone
and I could have brought her on in the
beginning. I said, "You know what? It's
important that you go on at the end
because she's the only one I know that
has visited Julina Assange maybe 40 or
50 times since 2013. She's been a not
you.
Oh,
you're keeping the place. You're paying
the rent.
She's
uh but u she uh brought me to Julian
Assange in 2016 when I was at WBAI. I
was looking for a guest and she said
here I I didn't want to ask her because
she had been visiting and she'd been
working with Michael Ratner uh on the
Assange case and uh so he got on my show
and then we did the Assange countdown
and she helped me coordinate it along
with Julia uh back in on April 11, 20
and so she last visited Julian Assange
four or five months months ago. Uh she's
been, if you take a look at her record,
uh 50 years going back to uh as a
organizer of the uh demonstrations and
the sitins at Columbia University
against the Vietnam War. She was person
of the week on ABC News for her work uh
with those in uh peace groups that were
infiltrated by the FBI. And I can't I
mean the list goes on and on but she
does it unlike her husband who the late
William Kler who got a lot of attention.
She does it quietly and she gets it
done. She worked with me on the uh
Rockefeller drug law movement. She got
me into Tulya where we got 46 people out
of prison that were shankied into it
this racist drugs drug thing in 1999.
uh but she does it quietly. uh but she
knows Assange and I think it's
appropriate that she is the last speaker
before we go out with Lucy Murphy and
that is the great attorney civil rights
attorney Margaret Rackard
[Music]
Is that working? All right.
Yes, it worked very well.
Am I supposed to talk or something?
All right, she's up there. Steve,
thank you, Steve.
You know,
the first time I spoke u
the first time I spoke in this room, I
said, you know what? I'm optimistic. I'm
optimistic that Julian is going to be
successful.
And the reason I'm optimistic is that
it's impossible that this country would
turn its back on the basic things, the
only things that are left to it to be
proud of. And that is the first
amendment. The ability to speak, the
ability to criticize, the ability to
choose who you want to elect on the
basis of knowing what they have to say
instead of hearing lies from everyone.
So I I said, you know, I stood up here
and I said, I'm optimistic and and I'm
embarrassed
that I said that. I really am because
how could I have been optimistic in the
face of looking at what this country has
done over the last 15 years? How do I
dare have optimism
at that at that point? I mean, I I know
I had optimism because it was a clean
fight because it meant free speech
because they grabbed somebody who wasn't
an American from another country and
said, "We can stop you from talking
about what we don't want to hear by
putting you in jail. Meanwhile, we can
keep you in isolation for 10 years while
we're readying our complaint against
you." So, okay, it's all okay. We can do
all of these things. I'm saying they
can't get away with this. This is not
possible. This is a white man. He has
nothing to do with with this society.
The only thing he's done is speak out,
publish things. He's done he's not a gun
runner. He's not a drug addict. He's not
selling drugs. He's not stealing
anything. He's not committing any crime.
So it's not possible that you can grab
him and put him in jail for the rest of
his life.
Well,
it is possible.
It is very possible. And I hate to say
this because I want to be, you know,
totally optimistic. Um, and I haven't
always been totally optimistic uh about
uh what could happen to my clients. And
I've been um
usually not disappointed because the
worst things happened and that was
expected. But I didn't expect the worst
thing to happen here.
And as you look around
today,
today it's worse than ever. So we can
see why it happened. We I you know last
year I didn't see why, but now I see
why. I see that this country has
deteriorated to such an extent that if
they can't control what is said, they
can't start
because they have done so many
and they have to do it without anybody
knowing or anybody talking about it
because
they can't survive and capitalism cannot
survive without their doing what they're
doing. So it's a there's a problem here.
So it's you know it's just an extension
of the problem of imperialism
and the problem of capitalism and
imperialism and it's all going to be
over very soon and I'm sorry to say
that. And we'll have a real hero in the
next millennium perhaps and that will be
Julian Assange.
and we will have someday statues for him
but not not in my life.
Um
he is a brilliant,
wonderful, generous human being who
really never harmed a soul in his life
and only had nice things to say about
everybody, believe it or not. And um
I never saw him be chauvinist. I never
saw him be um
talk nastily about anybody behind the
back.
And here he is having been tortured
and and um vilified and made into an
enemy so that the United States can get
away with this [__] And here we are in
a world that is unrecognizable now. And
um I'm sorry to say it, you know, and um
I don't know what else to say except
that, you know, I really love him and I
hope that you all can love him and how
see perceive
that how terrible this world has become
through looking at what's happening to
him.
um and what's happening to um
a large number of people in this room
who have been silenced
and why have they been silenced? Because
they're talking about what is truthfully
happening and we can't allow that
anymore. And what does that mean? What
what happens then? Can we
can we take to the streets?
Well, it's the only thing we can do. Um,
and will we do that? And that's that's
the question. Will we organize enough to
take to the streets and do something
about what is happening to this country?
And I don't know. I hope so. And that's
all I have to say.
Wow.
Margaret Country
because you are a lawyer and I was just
mentioning this to Steve, but he's going
to be tried in in this district which I
think John mentioned is loaded totally
loaded against him. Is there any way
that there's a way to demand that the
venue of this trial be changed? Is that
something that might at least be
It's like the guys that were tried in
the uh
the It's like the guys that were tried
uh in the attempt to kill Hitler in 45.
It was in It was in one judge's
courtroom and they couldn't get a change
of opinion.
All right.
No, no. You understand why? I
understand. It's a it's something you do
when when the court is stacking here
again.
It's you know you ask I mean I'm just
wondering and John I think it was John
who was talking about it is that
John can can they get a change of venue?
No,
no. Because they they'll argue that the
that the crime was committed in the
Eastern District of Virginia because
much of the information that was
released
was that it still should not be
something that people talk about and
reveal why this is a unfair
what's his name? Gordon Croberg.
Wow.
Gordon Croberg. Is that his name? The
prosecutor.
Oh, the prosecutor.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's his name. He's uh if you
ever saw late, he's a guy.
Even with what you said, there are all
kinds of times where a a trial is moved.
Oh, yes.
Because even though that's where it's
not happening here,
it is argued that they couldn't get a
fair trial there. Absolutely, right?
Yes.
I think it needs to be argued.
How many years is that going to take?
How much longer can he survive? There
are many things that can be argued. Why
do we do that?
There are many things that can be
argued.
No, would you relax, please?
Um, I'm
going to answer this question.
Um,
nothing that has happened to Julian
Assange has follows any law or follows
any reason.
I don't know why we should have I I mean
I was the same way. I I well this time
he's got to win because and I kept
saying that but it's not that way
anymore. The world doesn't operate on
the basis of justice on the basis of
well it wouldn't be fair if he were
trying here. That's meaningless now
obviously
but isn't it part of educating the
public
to to have at least a group challenging
this because you talk about why this
venue is so poisonous right and you know
you picking one thing but we could have
argued we argued all along about what
was happening to Julian we argued all
along about people who were kept in
Guantanamo we argued all along about
murders and and and the ways we kill
innocent civilians all over this world
and we talk about it, but does that
control it? Does that stop it? I mean,
we could talk about it and I agree that
if it didn't happen, we wouldn't talk
about it,
but it happens. We talk about it.
All right.
Oh, no. No censorship. Okay. No, I I
just you know the thing about it is he
said I just think if indeed he is going
to be tried in this venue that we cannot
be silent about how corrupt
this is. I agree. you know, and and
that's why we have to organize and we're
going to begin tomorrow morning in front
of the DOJ tomorrow morning uh afternoon
in the morning to go in front of the
center and Paula is going to come up
here and I want you to uh get your give
her your name and how you can get the
events because we have to continue to
organize. It's not going to happen on
television. It's not going to happen at
this event. It's not going to happen
anywhere but on the streets. That's if
you want to fight, be a winter soldier,
as Thomas Payne said, and get out there
in
110° weather, 21 below weather, and get
out there and fight because this is the
the end of this dem this what is this a
democracy? No, but I know that. But any
kind of
as John Pill just said any cintillaa of
a democratic uh society that we live in
in the west I don't it doesn't exist
whether it be Belgium you know you know
Netherlands the UK n it doesn't exist
okay it's all for public consumption but
you got to get please she's going to go
around and get your names here uh and
we're going to have Lucy Murphy come up
here and Lucy Murphy who has been at so
many of these Assange events and other
events. I last saw her at one for my uh
my uh for Assange and and the great
Linder Peltier and for uh Mia. I know. I
know.
I was going to forget that. All right.
So, um we're going to She's going to
close it. We got a couple of tunes for
Steve to Jones and we may get a a
speaker here or there for a couple of
seconds, but we got to close down the
live stream and move on and and we're
going to give it to Lucy Murphy right
now. Would you please stand?
Thank you, Margaret. Margaret wants to
give her a round of applause.
That was beautiful. Here,
let's go out with some music.
Thank you, Randy.
[Music]
locked in jail.
No one should hold their face. Keep your
eyes on the prize.
Hold on.
Oh,
[Music]
hold on.
Mary we and mother moan. Gel stood up
and blown on
your eyes.
[Applause]
Hold on.
Oh,
[Music]
keep your eyes on the prize.
Oh Lord,
the only thing that we did wrong was the
wonder in the wilderness
too long. Keep your heart open.
Hold on.
Keep your eyes.
[Music]
And the only thing that we did right was
to all that night that might keep your
eyes on Friday. Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on.
[Music]
You know, silence begin to shift.
They walk out. Keep your eyes on.
Hold on.
[Music]
Keep on.
Hold on.
[Music]
Keep your eyes on.
Hold on.
Yes.
In the key of E.
Okay.
[Music]
A little
voice.
[Music]
Okay, I think we have to rehearse this.
That's a call and response song.
It's a bushwad town.
It's a bushw.
And for you students, I expect you to
do. I got the bush blues. I'm going to
spread the news all around.
We'll try this again.
[Music]
Home down in Washington DC cuz it's
awesome.
[Music]
I'm going to spread the news.
all around.
[Music]
You know, we
went all over town. Everywhere we went,
the folks were turning us down.
Boob town.
It's a town.
It's a boob town.
I got the push balloons are going to
spread the news all the ground.
But let's stop first. Well, it's the
home of the brave and the stand of the
free. I don't want the Christmas tree.
But it's a bushwre.
[Music]
And this is the verse that got me in
trouble with Mary and Mary.
After
I sang this song,
all right,
there was this
where my name was,
my name got whited out and they didn't
even close the list. They just never
rich in Washington. He knows how to
throw a nickel to the mayor just to see
him at a bush town.
It's a good town.
I got the news
around
Washington. He knows how to throw a
nickel to the m just to see her bow cuz
it's a bush town.
It's a town.
I got the voice
going
around. Do you hear what I'm telling
you? I got the voice.
I'm going to use all.
[Music]
Wow. Oh yeah.
Don't go anywhere.
I want everybody that spoke tonight to
get up on the stage right now. And I
also want to thank Ford Fiser over here
who did the lighting, has done all of
these events, not just here, but has
done it uh throughout the city for all
progressive causes. That's sportfisher.
If you need live streaming, go to Fort
Fiser. He is absolutely the best. He's
committed and he's cheap.
Thanks, Randy.
No, no, but no, not cheap. No, he's he's
expensive.
Thanks, Randy.
No, he's committed. He wants the right
amount that likes what they're doing and
it's not a business. All right. Thank
you, Ford Fisher, for this. How do
people reach you?
News to share.
All right. I want everybody getting up
here. Margaret Ratner Hunster
and No, you you were up here.
Everyone to stay. John Kiryaku open the
show.
Uh and then we had uh John O'Donnell.
We had John O'Donnell. And then we had
Elanar
Hill.
Anybody
[Music]
[Applause]
get this table
everybody? Is everybody out there?
Spread it out.
All right.
Let's spread it out. I want to introduce
you once again.
And
Marvin Bradford
Sophia
Donald
This is right now in our gold field and
they are the best. All right, thank you
for
all and of course over here.
All right, thank you all uh for being a
part of this. We're all going to go back
there and uh hang out in the back of the
room.
Hold a sign early.
Yes, let's hold a sign. That would be a
great This is a sign by NYC Assange
which co sponsored this event tonight.
Thank you. And let's
Julian, let's try to get RT and this
great show back on.
Bring
it on. Bring it on.
Thank you all. Thank you, Tabern. Thank
you, Princy going. If you want to get
this picture, go ahead.
Dave, Ruby, I love you, man. And I see
Wire Green out there. And I see uh Nick
is out there. Brianna People's Party.
I'm going to run.
[Music]
around.
[Applause]
[Music]
All right.